[
    {
        "questionText": "answered Date",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "text",
        "answer": ""
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Candidate Name",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "text",
        "answer": "Jerry Green"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "disability form selection",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "checkbox",
        "answer": "I do not have a disability"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Ethnicity",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "select",
        "answer": "Asian"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Race",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "select",
        "answer": "Asian"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Experience:",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "authorized to work",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Are you currently authorized",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "visa sponsorship",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "W2 position",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Will you be able to relocate",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Will you be able to reliably commute",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "How many years of",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "number",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is the highest level of education",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "Master's"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "What is your highest level of completed education",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "Masters Degree or higher"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "following US states",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Do you speak",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "text",
        "answer": "English"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Do you speak",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Gender",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "Male"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "you are a U.S. Citizen",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "checkbox",
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Do you have experience with",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "textarea",
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "list all active certifications",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "textarea",
        "answer": "AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Certification",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "checkbox",
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Do you have experience with",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "checkbox",
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "desired salary",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "text",
        "answer": "$9000 / month"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Have you been previously employed at",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Please confirm your legal first and last name",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "text",
        "answer": "Jerry Green"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "located in",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Are you open to",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Have you ever held",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "U.S. citizenship",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "active security clearance",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "desired compensation",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "text",
        "answer": "$9000 / month"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "level of security clearance",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "select",
        "answer": "Background Check"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Recent Job Title",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "text",
        "answer": "Lead Full Stack Developer"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Recent Employer",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "text",
        "answer": "Soft Elegance"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "number to receive text",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "text",
        "answer": "+13465610919"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "It is okay to send me text messages",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "proceed with this",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Have you",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "Checkbox",
        "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "assistance",
        "optionalQuestion": false,
        "inputType": "radio",
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Current Location",
        "optionalQuestion": true,
        "inputType": "text",
        "answer": "Killeen, TX"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "Where are you located",
        "optionalQuestion": true,
        "inputType": "textarea",
        "answer": "Killeen, TX"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "phone",
        "optionalQuestion": true,
        "inputType": "text",
        "answer": "+13465610919"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "address",
        "optionalQuestion": true,
        "inputType": "textarea",
        "answer": "Killeen, TX"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "city",
        "optionalQuestion": true,
        "inputType": "text",
        "answer": "Killeen"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "state",
        "optionalQuestion": true,
        "inputType": "text",
        "answer": "TX"
    },
    {
        "questionText": "zip",
        "optionalQuestion": true,
        "inputType": "text",
        "answer": "76549"
    }
]